CHAPTER 1 - DOWN THE RABBIT HOLE: ALICE IS BORED SITTING ON THE 
RIVERBANK WITH HER SISTER, WHEN SHE NOTICES A TALKING, CLOTHED WHITE 
RABBIT WITH A POCKET WATCH RUN PAST. SHE FOLLOWS IT DOWN A RABBIT HOLE 
WHEN SUDDENLY SHE FALLS A LONG WAY TO A CURIOUS HALL WITH MANY LOCKED 
DOORS OF ALL SIZES. SHE FINDS A SMALL KEY TO A DOOR TOO SMALL FOR HER TO 
FIT, BUT THROUGH WHICH SHE SEES AN ATTRACTIVE GARDEN. SHE THEN DISCOVERS 
A BOTTLE LABELLED 'DRINK ME', THE CONTENTS OF WHICH CAUSE HER TO SHRINK 
TOO SMALL TO REACH THE KEY. A CAKE WITH 'EAT ME' ON IT CAUSES HER TO 
GROW TO SUCH A TREMENDOUS SIZE HER HEAD HITS THE CEILING.

